kabbalah.info 2019-08-28

# Privacy Policy | kabbalah.info

Last Modified May 24, 2018.

Bnei Baruch Association is a not-for-profit, non commercial organization (collectively, "[Kabbalah](https://www.kabbalah.info/)[.info](https://www.kabbalah.info/)", all websites linked from "[Kabbalah International](https://www.kab.info/ "Kabbalah International")," "We", or "Us") believe that your personal information belongs to you. This Website Policy ("Privacy Policy") shall apply solely to your access to, and use of, the Bnei Baruch's websites located at [www.kabbalah.info](https://www.kabbalah.info/), [edu.kabbalah.info](https://edu.kabbalah.info/) as well as any other Bnei Baruch controlled sites, e.g. [The Kabbalah Channel,](https://tv.kabbalah.info/) [Kab TV](https://www.kab.tv/ "Kabbalah TV"), [Kabbalah International](https://www.kab.info/ "Kabbalah International"),[Kabbalah Publication](https://www.kabtoday.com/ "Kabbalah Publication"), [Kabbalah Blog](https://www.kabbalahblog.info/ "Kabbalah Blog") and [Kabbalah Books](https://www.kabbalahbooks.info/ "Kabbalah Books"), regardless of domain name or IP address (collectively "Site" or "Sites") and the features and applications accessible through the Sites (collectively the "Services"). We collect this type of information to serve you better when you provide it to us, but we do not rent or sell your information to third parties. We do not affiliate ourselves with any third party program and/or organization. We do not partner with or have special relationships with any ad server companies. From time to time, we may ask if you are interested in receiving information from third parties whose services or information we think would be of value to you. In those instances, we will only disclose your email address or other personal information to third parties  **if you expressly consent to such disclosure**.

**About This Policy**

This Policy sets out the essential details relating to your personal data relationship with Bnei Baruch. The Policy applies to all Bnei Baruch services and any associated services (referred to collectively as the ‘Services). The terms governing your use of the Services are defined in our [Terms and Conditions of Use](https://www.kabbalah.info/engkab/homepage/terms).

From time to time, we may develop new or offer additional services. If the introduction of these new or additional services results in any change to the way we collect or process your personal data we will provide you with more information and additional terms or policies. Unless stated otherwise when we introduce these new or additional services, they will be subject to this Policy.

The aim of this Policy is to:

\- Ensure that you understand what personal data we collect about you, the reasons why we collect and use it, and who we share it with;

\- Explain the way we use the personal data that you share with us in order to give you a great experience when you are using the Services; and

\- Explain your rights and choices in relation to the personal data we collect and process about you and how we will protect your privacy.

We hope this helps you understand our privacy commitments to you. For information on how to contact us if you ever have any questions or concerns, please see the ‘How to Contact Us’ section below. Alternatively, if you do not agree with the content of this Policy, then please remember it is your choice whether you want to use Bnei Baruch’s Services.

**Our Collection of Information**

**Information Collected Directly From You**

You can visit this Website, without entering any personal information. However, in order to access certain information or to take advantage of special programs or features that may be contained on the Website, we may require you to provide certain personal information. For example, we will collect certain personal information such as your email address and name if you choose to join our mailing list, or your email address, name, city and country if you subscribe to our learning environment [edu.kabbalah.info](https://edu.kabbalah.info/), any of our email or mobile content delivery programs, or if you choose to write and/or rate reviews of various products

In certain instances, other demographic data may be collected. Kabbalah.info uses this information to provide benefits and/or services associated with its various programs or features and Kabbalah.info uses such information to further improve user experience.

**Information Collected Automatically**

We may collect information about your visit to the Website, including what pages you view, the number of bytes transferred, the links you click, the materials you access, and other actions taken within the Website. We may also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your Internet Protocol address, your browser type and capabilities and language, your operating system, the date and time you access the Websites, and the website from which you linked to our Websites. From time to time, we may use this information to improve user experience, optimize promotional offers of products and/or services.

Additionally, Kabbalah.info and/or our service providers may collect your click-stream data and other preference information. We do this to improve the design of the Website. Click-stream data represents a page-by-page history of your website usage. Your preference data includes reminder, search, and other information-related information that you submit to the site.

**Our Use of Information**

In order to offer you a more consistent experience in your interactions with Kabbalah.info, information collected via the Website may be combined with information we collect by other means. We may also use your personal information to improve the Website, to optimize our offers of products and/or services, or to make the Website easier to use by eliminating the need for you to repeatedly enter the same information or by customizing the Website to your particular preference or interests.

If you have chosen to receive communications by email from us but later wish to opt-out of receiving such communications from us at any time, simply follow the instructions for doing so included in the emails.

If you would like to opt-out of receiving any program-related and other direct mail from us, please send a written request to:  
In Unites States of America please write to:

Bnei Baruch America, Inc.  
7253 Watson Rd.  
Suite 1031  
Saint Louis, MO 63119  
E-mail: maillist@kbb1.com

In Canada please write to:  
Bnei Baruch Canada  
4630 Dufferin street, Suite 301,  
Toronto, ON, M3H 5S4 Canada  
E-mail: maillist@kbb1.com

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Website, or any of our email subscription or mobile content delivery programs, such as service announcements or similar administrative or transactional messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

**Our Use of Cookies; Affiliate Party Cookies; Web Beacons**

Cookies are small files that websites save to your hard disk or to your browser's memory. We may use them to track the number of times you have visited the Website, to track the number of visitors to the Website, to determine and analyze visitors' use of the Websites, to store information that you provide such as your preferences, and to store technical information useful for your interactions with the Website.

The Website uses both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. Session cookies are used to make it easier for you to navigate the site. A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser's "help" file. Persistent cookies are set to store an encrypted link to your account information, so you don't have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable Kabbalah.info to track and target the interests of users to enhance the experience on the site(s).

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser settings to decline cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being placed on your computer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the features of the Website.

Our Website also may contain electronic images known as web beacons-sometimes called single-pixel gifs-that allow us to count the number of users who have visited those pages. We may include web beacons in promotional email messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

**When You Subscribe to KABBALAH.INFO Email Programs**

You can choose to receive email from us by signing up on our Website. When you sign up for email, we will send you information about our affiliated companies based on the preferences you have set. The emails we send will include special offers, promotions, updates on services offered, invitations to join other promotional programs, and notification of upcoming events. To ensure that we are providing materials of interest to you, we may monitor whether you opened a particular email and whether you have clicked on the images and/or links therein.

Our HTML-based email messages include an invisible coded sensor that is activated when the email message is opened. This sensor communicates the date and time the message was opened and, more importantly, whether your computer is capable of receiving HTML-based email. You will receive a functioning sensor only if your computer is enabled to accept HTML email.

You may unsubscribe at any time from our email programs by clicking on the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any email message. All unsubscribe requests will be honored within thirty (30) days. At any time, users may opt-out of Kabbalah.info correspondence by sending an email to [maillist@kbb1.com](mailto:maillist@kbb1.com)

**User Submitted Content**

All user communications made to or through Kabbalah.info or kabbalah.info controlled sites are referred to as "User-Submitted Content." To comment on any portion of Kabbalah.info, we encourage you to first register with Kabbalah.info and agree to our Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions. However, submitting requests for contact do not require registering with Kabbalah.info. By submitting content, you agree that:

  * Your submitted content is not illegal, indecent, profane, threatening, or defamatory; and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings or any form of "spam."  

  *  Your submitted content does not infringe on the copyright, trademark or other intellectual property rights of any person or entity, or contain any confidential or proprietary information of any person or entity, or otherwise violate the legal rights of any person or entity.  

  *  Your submitted content does not contain personally identifiable information about other persons, such as their phone number, contact information or email address, or information about that could result in an invasion of their privacy or their harassment.  

  *  You grant us a non-exclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable and fully assignable and sub-licensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, edit, reformat, create derivative works from, distribute and display content throughout the world for any purpose and in any media (including for advertising or other commercial use).  

  *  If we publish your content or authorize or license others to do so, your content may be edited for length or clarity or for any other reason either before or after it is published. We reserve the right (but not the obligation) to remove any content for any reason from Kabbalah.info.

**Disclosure of Your Personal Information**

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, personal information you provide to Kabbalah.info through the Website or any of our email subscription or mobile content delivery programs, will not be shared outside of our company and its service providers without your express permission. "Company" means the Bnei Baruch Kabbalah Education & Research Institute, Bnei Baruch Association, Bnei Baruch America, Kabbalah.info and Bnei Baruch Israel (Kabbalah L'Am). 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure your personal information. However, "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet, and there is always some risk in transmitting information electronically. The personal information we collect is stored within databases that we control directly or through our service providers. As we deem appropriate, we use security measures consistent with industry standards, such as firewalls and encryption technology, to protect your information. However, since no security system is impenetrable, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply will not be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Of course, any information you post to any message board, discussion group, or other public posting area on our Website is available to anyone with Internet access.

We recommend that you do not disclose your account information or your password to any other person. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and account, and you are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or account.

**Links to Other Sites**

Kabbalah.info Website contains links to affiliate websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. If you submit any personal information to an affiliate website or transact a purchase after clicking on a link from Kabbalah.info Website, you are not submitting that information to Kabbalah.info and Kabbalah.info has no control over the collection and/or disclosure of that submitted information. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to familiarize themselves with the privacy statements of every website that collects personally information.

**Children's Privacy**

We do not seek or knowingly collect any personal information about children under 13 years of age. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected personal information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database. It is our policy to endorse the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 and to use our best efforts to comply with that Act.

**In Summary**

Kabbalah.info is committed to protecting your privacy. Kabbalah.info does not sell, trade, give away, or rent personal or company information, including email address, to any outside parties in ways other than disclosed in this Privacy Policy. Kabbalah.info uses the information collected on the site to make promotional activities possible and to enhance your overall experience with our Website.

**Governing Law; Visitors Residing Outside the United States**

This Privacy Policy and the privacy practices of Kabbalah.info will be subject exclusively to the laws of the State of New York within the United States of America, without regard to its conflict of law principles. Kabbalah.info makes no representation that this Privacy Policy and such practices comply with the laws of any other country. Visitors who use the Website and reside outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. If you reside outside of the United States, by using our Website, you consent to the transfer and use of your information outside your country. Without limiting the foregoing, by providing any personal information to Kabbalah.info, all Website visitors, including, without limitation, Website visitors in the member states of the European Union, fully understand and unambiguously consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection, storage, and processing of such information in the United States of America.

**GDPR Disclaimer**

As of May 25, 2018, the Bnei Baruch Services are fully compliant with GDPR.

GDPR extends the data privacy rights of all European individuals and gives them the power to better control their data. Companies that provide services, and process personal data of these European individuals, must comply with all GDPR set of regulations. There are specific and clear requirements that these companies must meet, and basic rights that European individuals can exercise with these companies. More information about GDPR can be found in the official GDPR European Union’s website:

<https://ec.europa.eu/info/law/law-topic/data-protection/data-protection-eu_en>

**Data Protection Officer:**

We appointed a Data Protection Officer to manage and supervise the fulfillment of all GDPR requirements, and assist any inquiries from individuals. The DPO can be reached at [info@kabbalah.info](mailto:info@kabbalah.info).

Functions to support GDPR requirements:

Bnei Baruch is committed to assist all customers managing their archived data.

You may also choose to permanently delete all your data by sending such a request to [info@kabbalah.info.](mailto:info@kabbalah.info)

**Updates to this Policy**

We reserve the right to update our Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will post a notice on the Websites for a reasonable period of time after such changes are made that this Privacy Policy has been updated and we will revise the "Last Modified" date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any updates. Your continued use of the Websites following the posting of updates to this Privacy Policy will mean you accept those updates.

**Contact Us**

Any questions you may have regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed via email to [info@kabbalah.info](mailto:info@kabbalah.info). You can also write us at:

In Unites States of America please write to:  
Bnei Baruch America, Inc.  
7253 Watson Rd.  
Suite 1031  
Saint Louis, MO 63119

In Canada please write to:  
Bnei Baruch (Toronto) Inc.  
4630 Dufferin street, Suite 301,  
Toronto, ON, M3H 5S4 Canada
